Still, we won't give up!
Together we can go anywhere
Yes! This is our world
Even if I'm scared, or cry
Don't worry! Smile
You're not alone
Let's find it! A shining smile
That's the real treasure!
Let's go, Kasukabe Guard!
India?
The place famous for curry?
Yes. In Mushibai, Hagashimir province
there's an entertainment festival
every year.
With musicals, singing and dancing.
Wow! Awesome.
A girl named Ariana
who performed last year
is very popular in India right now.
Really? She's pretty.
To celebrate our upcoming
sister city relationship,
our town will hold the Kasukabe Kids
Entertainment Festival.
The winners will get invited to India
and get to dance on stage.
To India? For free?
Yes! We, the Kasukabe Guard should join
and represent Futaba Kindergarten!
Sounds fun.
But I wonder if we can do it.
Masao! Let's give it a dry.
It's "Let's give it a try".
I want to eat curry
with a cute Indian lady.
I wanna go to India too!
Agreed!
Yeah, me too!
Then it's decided.
Let's all go to India!
Yeah!
Shin chan, you're not practicing?
I'm too busy with this right now.
We've been practicing all the time.
I want to play 'real house'.
I have an English test today.
I've got to study.
Hey, guys! Look.
Naan.
Huh? Naan bread?
Yep, it's naan bread.
Dancing all together in India
sounds like soooo much fun!
It's a once in a lifetime chance.
You're right.
If we don't win, we won't be able to go.
Let's give it our all!
Jeez, Kazama. You always skip practice.
That's you.
(Kasukabe Kids Entertainment Festival)
Together we can go anywhere
Yes! This is our world
Even if I'm scared, or cry
Don't worry! Smile
You're not alone
Let's find it! A shining smile
That's the real treasure!
Yay!
Namaste!
(Crayon Shinchan the Movie:
Super Hot! The Spicy Kasukabe Dancers)
We're in India!
Let's hold hands so we don't get lost.
Bo! Shinnosuke!
Don't run, it's dangerous.
Hey, Shinnosuke! Wait!
Nice stone.
Himawari, thank you for coming
all the way here.
Stop it, Hima.
I'm sorry we brought the whole family.
Sorry.
No, I really appreciate it.
I can't lead the trip by myself.
I wish my mom and dad could come too.
My parents can't get any time off.
Mine either.
Adults can't take time off
at short notice.
I'm jealous.
Shin chan's dad doesn't have work.
I do have a job, you know.
The company won't have any problem
without him, that's all.
Shinnosuke, the truth can hurt people.
Even Shiro's here.
Shiro is family, too.
Who is he?
He's taking us to Mushibai.
He's our guide, Mr. Mhm Uh-huh.
Mhm.
Uh-huh!
Wow, what's this?
It's chai, right?
Uh-huh.
It's milk tea made by boiling tea leaves
and adding spices later.
You know your stuff, boss.
I've done my research.
Namaste.
Namaste is an Indian greeting, right?
Yeah. It means 'hello' or 'goodbye.'
Kazama, can you take a look
at my special namaste?
Special namaste?
Speaking of India...
An Indian elephant, toot!
Namaste!
That's no elephant!
Silly.
I laughed so hard
that my nose ran more than usual.
I say the important things
in elephant form, you know.
Kazama,
you're stepping on cow poop, toot.
My shoe's all dirty!
Oops. It's okay, don't worry.
I've got some water. I'll wash it off.
It happens often in India, right?
Uh-huh.
Bo, look! Look!
We should perform like this on stage.
A key?
That means...
What's this?
A nose...
...backpack?
Shin chan, it suits you.
This, snooze.
"Please"!
I found it over there.
I'm rich.
I've got one million thousand yen!
Please, keep the change.
Maybe it's not enough.
Noselina Jolie. Nice!
Noselina Jolie?
The name of this nose.
Use it whenever you want.
Noselina is half your nose.
Thank you.
Put together it looks like a heart.
A butt-looking stone!
Here, let's share the butt.
Are you sure?
My sideburn of India.
It's "souvenir".
Same difference.
Difference same.
Let's find it! A shining smile
That's the real treasure!
The show is in two days.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
The world will finally know
how cute I am.
Yeah.
I'm getting nervous.
It's too early.
Don't worry! There are many more
people in India than in Kasukabe.
They'll be watching you.
Don't say that!
Dancing all together! It'll be fun!
Heave ho.
I'm back. Did you sell anything?
Just a sale item.
Welcome.
- We're looking for the 'paper'.
- Huh?
It looks like simple tissue paper,
but in truth...
According to my deduction,
it should be sealed in a case like this.
I've never seen it!
It's not in this store!
So it is here.
You're always right, Big Bro.
I said it's not here!
I'm terribly busy. Come on, leave.
It's no use.
You can't keep secrets from us.
Right, Big Bro?
Say the truth
Just say it, and you'll feel better
3-2-1, go! Say it
If you say it, you'll feel better
Shake your shoulders and sing. Yeah!
Step, step, let's dance. Come on!
Open your mouth and say it
Uuups!
Is it up there? Right? Left?
No, no, no, no!
Is it here? There? Over there?
That 'paper' is a monstrosity
That has to stay locked up
The one and only, diabolically evil
Bizarre and mysterious
Horrifying and earth-shattering
It won't be in there!
So where is it?
That 'paper'...
It's not there!
I just sold this.
Who did you sell it to?
Two foreigners. A butt-shaking kid,
and a snotty boy.
Butt-shaking?
Snotty?
They look like this.
If that gets stuck in someone's nose,
something terrible will happen.
Heave ho.
It takes 15 hours to reach Mushibai.
Time will fly.
This train has an observation deck.
Let's go explore!
Let's go!
Can you take a photo of me with
a beautiful view and send it to my mom?
Sure.
Can I send you a photo of me
with a beautiful lady, Mom?
No, thanks.
Say "Cheese."
I'll send it to your moms.
Um, what time is it in Japan?
Well, whatever.
Huh? That was fast!
I guess they're worried.
Look! Look!
It's very different from Kasukabe.
India is so dynamic.
I wanna see it too.
Hey ladies, I'm Shinnosuke Nohara.
Wanna eat some hot steamy curry with me?
Stop it, Shinnosuke.
Sorry, sorry! I'm sorry!
Huh? What was I...?
Jeez, you're so silly.
We came all the way to India. Behave.
I need the bathroom.
Huh? What was I...?
I got the Old Maid.
Two old men playing Old Maid. Nice!
Mr. Uh-huh, care to join us?
Uh-huh.
We're back with a crash!
Don't say scary things.
It's "back with a bang."
How was the observation deck?
Great!
Let's go together later.
Good idea.
Found it! Curry Flavor Chocobi.
Have some, Bo. Let's have a toast!
I'm star-star-starving.
Stop.
No snacks before lunch.
You're so stingy, Mom.
I'm fine with that.
I wanna eat it! I wanna eat it!
You're a good boy, Bo.
The train will do a 30-minute stop
at the next station.
Let's go buy lunch all together.
Thanks to the sketch,
I was able to identify the kids
from security camera footage and
track them down by facial recognition.
They're currently on a train
bound for Mushibai.
That's the train.
Butt-shaking boy and snotty boy
are on that train.
You're the best, Big Bro.
We'll prevent anyone to stick
that 'paper' up their nose!
Roger.
Lord Urufu! It's dangerous!
It was caught in the jungle 2 days ago.
I'm just saying hello.
To my potential partner.
My buddy must be strong.
Do you have what it takes
to be my partner?
I want curry!
There are so many kinds of curry.
Mr. Uh-huh, I'd like to order
some mild curry for the kids.
Uh-huh.
Hmm... hmm...
Rice? Naan? Chapati?
Chapati?
Chapati chapati chapati chapati...
That's "kabaddi".
He's making chapati.
Chapati is made from whole wheat flour
kneaded with water
and baked. It's commonly eaten
in Indian households.
Right?
Uh-huh.
Looks delicious!
Is chapati delicious?
Yes.
Right. Then I'll have...
Naan.
I'd like some rice.
I want naan, too.
Naan.
Let's have naan.
I'll have both rice and naan.
Naan. For you too?
Uh-huh.
I'll have...
Naan.
I can't sit down.
I'm so hungry my butt's gonna split.
What curry is it?
Smells good. Let me have a bite.
One bite, please. Gimme gimme.
One bite, please.
Really?
Real curry is not so bad either.
They all look delicious.
Bo, did you just do something?
What's happening to me?
Naan, rice, naan.
Naan and rice. Naan, naan, naan.
Chapati.
Chapati?
Well, okay.
Did you all get your food?
Yes.
Shin chan wanted naan.
He asked for naan, not chapati.
He ordered naan, but...
Bo, what's wrong?
My butt is so hungry.
Happy Masala curry!
It has to be naan!
Shin chan wanted to eat naan.
Naan! Naan!
- Naan!
- Bo just blew a gale!
Bo!
Hey!
The world's most terrifying
wild honey badger!
- What's that?
- How cute!
Bo! Look, we brought some naan.
We've got naan. Calm down now.
That's Shin chan's naan.
Give it back.
Shin chan's naan!
Bo is so fast!
Bo!
Calm down, Bo.
Mhm! Uh-huh!
Mr. Uh-huh, are you okay?
Wait a minute, Bo!
Oh, no!
It's already up his nose!
Only half of it. Don't give up!
Boy! Take that piece of paper
out of your nose.
Piece of paper?
Who are you?
Indian Police Unsolved Mysterious Cases
Special Investigation Unit Detective
Kabir Katchapapal Pakkapapal
Katchapapal Pakkapapal.
Same. Dill.
We're here to collect
some dangerous 'paper'.
Excellent Japanese.
We are the top elite
among India's 1.45 billion people.
I speak 12 languages.
Dill speaks all languages.
All languages?
So, say "I can walk on my butt"
in Indian.
Korean.
Akita dialect.
What are you making him do?
What paper?
The evil piece of paper
stuck in that boy's nose.
When you stick it up your nose,
all your energy concentrates there.
It makes you breathe hard,
and generates tremendous power.
That's right.
And it'll try to grant the desires
of the one who stuck it up their nose.
What?
When it gets stuck in both nostrils,
the boy will go out of control
to fulfill his desires,
turning into a brutal and barbaric
belligerent tyrant!
What? Bo will turn into a tyrant?
It's only up one nostril,
so he only has half the power.
We must take that 'paper'
out of his nose now!
Well said, Big Bro.
Naan!
Your naan, Shin chan.
Thanks a bunch.
It's just naan bread. Needs curry.
Curry for Shin chan!
Bo!
He's strong. I can't believe...
he subdued my potential partner,
the King of All Ratels.
Catch him!
Shin chan's curry. Shin chan's curry.
Shin chan hates green pepper.
He likes meat.
Bo!
And Tandoori chicken.
He likes rice too. And naan.
We have naan. We do.
Shin chan's curry. Shin chan's curry.
Shin chan's curry. He likes meat.
And fish. And shrimp.
Does he like onions?
Likes spicy food too, but not too spicy.
Shin chan's curry. Shin chan's curry.
What are you doing to the kids?!
We'll take care of it.
In one fell swoop.
Yeah.
We'll draw out
120% of our latent abilities.
This is the power of India!
Let's sing! India power!
Can you feel it? Inside me
Let's dance! India power!
I know it's there!
The power that lies dormant
Pushing forward
On the path of the unknown
We are Hot! Super spicy curry
Singing makes you strong
The drumbeat of your heart
Dancing lights up your passion
Limits? Common sense? Chai, chai, chai
They're powering up?
I don't care about shattered samosas
That's my song
Masala chai for spilled tears
That's my love song
Okay! Full throttle, top gear!
Let's sing! India power!
Are you feeling it? Inside me
Let's dance! India power!
Awaken! The power that lies dormant
Push forward to the unknown!
We are Hot!
Super spicy curry
India Power is amazing!
India power!
Oh, no!
The train!
Must go to Mushibai.
Bo?
We'll all join the festival.
Wait...
I'm starving.
No picking up food from the floor!
I'm amazing, aren't I?
I can even do this.
What happened to him?
I've never seen Bo like that before.
Wait, Bo!
I can do anything.
I'm amazing.
Bo! It's dangerous!
Pull that piece of paper out!
What?
You've gone weird because
of that tissue in your nose!
"Weird"?
I'm weird?
I'm not weird. Not at all.
I'm awesome now!
Bo...
Butt-shaking boy!
Throw that backpack this way!
Don't let snotty boy get the other
piece of paper at all costs!
There's another piece.
Two pieces and it'll be complete.
I want it. I want the other one too!
I want it! I want it!
The piece of paper up snotty boy's nose
is craving for the other piece!
Shiro!
Bo, what happened to you?
You're not yourself anymore!
Bo is calmer and gentler!
Yes! He's nicer!
And a good boy, too!
Bo!
Bo...
What do you know about me?
Bo?
What do you know about me!
I found a strongman.
Shinnosuke!
Dad!
Kabir Katchapapal Pakkapapal
Katchapapal Pakkapapal!
Dill!
Masao! Shiro!
Shinnosuke!
Where am I?
Dad! Mom!
This is Mushibai, in Hagashimir province.
Where the festival will take place.
Hi, Cube.
Yes, Sir?
Get the car. Autopilot.
As you wish.
Come to my castle. Hop on.
You're invited to my castle.
Please get in the car.
Don't be shy, Bo. You're my partner.
Right?
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Hiroshi!
Bo! Get away from him!
Let go of me, you bastard!
It's okay, Shin chan's mom and dad.
Huh?
I don't need to be protected
by anyone anymore.
Bo...?
Come on. Partner, up front.
The rest of you in the back.
What are you doing?
They're little kids!
- What?
- How dare you?
Hey, Bo!
Bo!
We have to go find
Shinnosuke and Masao!
I'll take care of it.
I'll prepare perfectly.
Prepare?
For the entertainment festival.
We came here to perform there.
We came here to perform
at the Entertainment Festival.
Right! Then let's buy
the whole festival for my partner, Bo!
Buy the whole festival?
That can't be possible...
This is the Amazing Cube.
I spent a trillion yen to develop it.
It allows me to instantly connect to
the entire world network via satellite
and do anything I want.
Now the festival is ours.
Do as you please.
Urufu & Bo Inc. presents
The Entertainment Festival!
No need to thank me.
I'm your partner.
Right?
Hey! Stay away from Bo!
Who the hell are you?
Hi, Cube.
Yes, Sir?
Start the music.
Yeah! Ho Ho
Gorgeous rich guy
Ya Ha Ha! Cool
I'll tell you about me.
The Ganges echoed with my first cry
I am Urufu the Perfect
The hottest man in India
Gorgeous rich guy
Kangchenjunga hair
A trillion yen is small change
Happiness, health, time
and sleeping in, I can buy it all
Everyone loves me
This perfect man has just one wish
The best partner
To share my path with
And many adventures
I finally found him
It's you, Mr. Bo!
Tell me what you need
and I'll give you everything.
I can't live without you now
You neither, right?
(That's a partner)
With you, I'll be super warm in winter
(That's a heater)
You always steal my heart
(That's a burglar)
What the heck?
Dill, you left me all alone...
You're a cop, right? Sing again
and do something with your India power!
Let's sing. India power...
Gloomy.
What exactly is that 'paper'?
You said it makes desires come true.
"I want to eat that."
"I want this."...
Human desire is immeasurable,
like the deep ocean.
I think that 'paper' gives the power
to make desires come true
to whoever sticks it in their nose.
The power to make desires come true?
Some say that, since ancient times,
people who are considered tyrants
might have been influenced
by that 'paper'.
The last time its existence
was recorded
was 35 years ago in India.
When an elephant destroyed a village
with just his nose.
An elephant?
It was a beautiful village
growing bananas.
Look! It's got two pieces of paper
stuck in its nose.
Maybe the elephant's desire
to eat bananas destroyed the village.
What will happen to Bo?
When the two pieces of paper are
fully inserted into both nostrils,
they'll become one with the boy,
and he'll turn into a tyrant.
I can't live without you now
You neither, right?
(That's a partner)
You can dam up
The muddy waters of sorrow
(That's a barrier)
What the heck is that?
Misae?
When I first saw that piece of paper,
I felt like I wanted it so bad...
But now I don't want it at all.
I suppose now that it has the boy
it doesn't have to tempt anyone anymore.
Now, in order to turn that boy
into a tyrant,
it only wants the other piece
of paper that butt-shaking boy has.
Shinnosuke has what?
The 'paper' is made of two pieces.
At this point, in order to prevent
the birth of a tyrant,
if butt-shaking boy would run somewhere
far away with his piece of paper...
His name is not "butt-shaking boy"!
Shinnosuke is...
my plump, smooth-skinned, butt-shaking
sweet and lovely boy...
Shinnosuke!
If you want to see it
I'll open up my heart
(That's dissection)
Um... I am a boy.
Yo!
Elephants.
Elephants...
Elephant, elephant.
I'm so popular.
Panic, panic, panic
Everyone's rushing around
I'm amazing, I'm a genius
Powerful, powerful, full power!
Hey, Misae
I'm enjoying my silly day
I'm fine!
If you want to hang out with the girls
Leave it to me
Three or four, you have to be passionate
Come on baby, come on baby
Can you eat onions?
You make me blush
If you stare at me
Elephant, elephant
I'm so popular
Namaste!
Panic, panic, panic
Everyone's rushing around
I'm amazing, I'm a genius
Got a bright future ahead of me
Come on baby, come on baby
Can you eat onions?
You make me blush
If you stare at me
Elephant, elephant
I'm so popular
Namaste!
Panic, panic, panic
Everyone's rushing around
I'm amazing, I'm a genius
Got a bright future ahead of me
Hey lady, do you like green peppers?
Can you eat carrots?
Do you put green onions in your natto?
I wish everyone happiness!
Great, Ariana. Fantastic work.
Make everyone happy with that smile
at this year's festival.
Thank you, I'll do my best.
Ariana is rehearsing!
- Let's go watch.
- Yeah.
Ariana is here!
- Ariana!
- Smile, Ariana!
You'll be on stage soon.
Mom and Dad will be cheering for you
from here.
Keep smiling. Do your best.
I know. We're leaving soon. Bye.
Always smile.
No one wants to see me depressed.
I'm smiling for someone else's sake
Being the beautiful me
Reflected in everyone's eyes
I want to keep shining
But I feel somewhat frustrated
I don't want to be hated
I just don't want to be alone
I'm always a good girl
I don't know what to do anymore
What?
Once again.
Here.
What?
When you're down, you should eat
something sweet and indulge yourself.
That's what my mom said.
I'm not down.
She can understand me?
I'm speaking Indian?!
I'm a genius!
I'm speaking Japanese.
I studied Japanese because I love anime.
Sparkle! A feeling of love!
Flutter!
Friendship! Love! Self-esteem!
'Shake Shake Bootycure!'
Wow! So you know about it.
I watch it with Himawari.
An ordinary girl faces up
to any challenge with her friends
for her and someone else's happiness.
Shake Shake Bootycure!
So cool!
I'm Bootycure Shinnosuke!
I'm Bootycure Ariana!
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for Bo and the others.
Bo?
This is hopeless.
Getting lost in India...
I can't speak the language,
and I don't have any money.
It's over.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I can't take care of a dog too!
I'll follow you anywhere, Master Shiro!
Bo, where are Shin chan's mom and dad?
Don't worry about them.
Shinnosuke...
Masao... Shiro...
Please be safe!
Dill...
Grown-ups have the duty to make curry.
Bo, what are you doing?
Preparing for the festival, of course.
My costumes, my songs.
I paid for everything.
Don't worry, it's a small price to pay.
I'm your one and only partner,
after all.
Right?
Hey, Bo. About that piece
of paper in your nose...
I think it's time to take it out.
If you don't, something bad will...
There's nothing bad. I'm doing great.
Bo, aren't you worried
about Shin chan and Masao?
- Shin chan!
- Shinnosuke!
Found him.
Looks like he's doing pretty well.
Thank goodness! Shinnosuke's okay.
So you've been looking for them.
Why didn't you tell us?
Found the 'paper'.
Wait for me, Shin chan.
So that boy called Bo
has stuck that 'paper' up his nose
and gained an incredible power
that can make any desire come true?
I guess so.
What would you do if you had the power
to make anything come true?
I'd...
lie around.
Then slack off, and snooze off.
What?
I guess you don't need that 'paper'.
What's that?
What are those?
Shin chan!
Bo!
The festival is about to start.
I've been looking for you.
Don't worry, I'll make sure
you get here safely.
So, do you have the 'paper'?
Do you have Noselina Jolie with you?
What's going on here?
Bo, are you in there?
I'm not.
Do you have the 'paper'?
Rare.
Earth.
Heart.
Tooth.
Heartache.
E... e...
It's not time to play word chain!
N? Namaste! I love India!
The 'paper'!
Good, you've got it.
You said that I can use Noselina
whenever I want, right?
Now it's the time.
I want the 'paper'.
I want the 'paper'. I want the 'paper'.
Bo?
Shin chan! Gimme the 'paper'.
Run, Shinnosuke!
Kazama?
You must not give Bo the 'paper'!
Dump it somewhere far away!
Stop it! Let go of me!
Kazama!
Watch out!
Don't interfere!
Ariana!
Shinnosuke! Behind you!
Shake shake!
We did it!
We're like the Bootycure!
That's right.
Shake Shake Bootycure!
Isn't that Ariana?
What? Ariana?
Ariana!
Shin chan, done.
Now let's find Masao.
What should we do with him?
Make him chop onions?
Let him go.
Let me go!
Are you okay, Kazama?
Yeah.
Bo, please!
Take that 'paper' out of your nose.
That's why you've gone weird!
I'm not weird.
Didn't you know?
This is the real me.
Nene!
Both of you,
change into your stage clothes.
The festival is about to begin.
Oh, man.
Are you okay?
Now I know how a package feels.
So, where are we?
I think it's flying back. If we stay
on board, we'll probably meet Bo.
Well, I guess I'll lie down, then.
- Is this Ariana?
- She'd never kick a dog.
- She's so nice. I can't believe it.
- I'd be disappointed.
- What's with the pose?
- Ain't right.
- I want to see her smile.
- It's not like her.
I'm smiling for someone else's sake
Being the beautiful me
Reflected in everyone's eyes
I want to keep shining
But I feel somewhat frustrated
I don't want to be hated
I just don't want to be alone
I'm always a good girl
I don't know
what to do anymore
I just smiled and laughed
This is how I should be, right?
The feelings I left behind
Are looping
The pent up feelings inside me
Swell up and my heart aches
I just smiled and laughed
This is how I should be
The feelings I pretended not to see
Are looping
Tell me, what is right?
What should I do?
What shall I do?
Tell me, what shall I do?
Why?
It should have been a fun festival.
Don't worry. It's gonna be alright.
Nene, let's do what you and I can do.
You're right.
Shinnosuke! Wake up.
Hm?
What's this place?
This is Bo's...
Maharaja Bo presents
the Entertainment Festival!
The world is at the mercy
of Maharaja Bo's desires.
No need to line up behind someone else.
(Bo will run wild at the front)
No one can stop someone else's freedom
A huge mountain of curry erupting!
(Boom! Drink and eat all you want)
The world is at the mercy
of Maharaja Bo's desires.
I'll just do what I want.
Sleep in like a log, bravo!
At Midnight.
(Out of control sunfish)
And I won't brush my teeth.
(Even if you get cavities?)
I don't care.
It's just baby teeth.
(Outrageous and defiant)
Nene, why aren't you dancing?
Kazama, I told you to change
into your stage costume, didn't I?
You promised.
You said we'd all dance together.
Dance.
-I refuse.
We're friends, right?
Because we are,
I'll tell you something.
You can't dictate someone's feelings.
We won't be dancing
to someone else's tune.
If you don't dance,
I'll have you chop onions.
Kazama!
Mommy!
Toru!
- Shin chan!
- Shinnosuke?
Are you okay?
Can't you show up more normally?
Hey! Why did you bring it here?
I told you to dump it far away!
No way I'll dump Noselina.
You're so mean, Kazama.
Bravo!
Welcome to the festival.
Bo, you've changed quite a lot
since the last time I saw you.
Kids grow up quickly, you know.
Shin chan, give me the 'paper'.
Then...
Let's all dance!
Bo!
Shin chan!
I want to see your runny nose!
No more snot for me.
Give me the 'paper'.
No.
This is the power of the 'paper'?
Shin chan!
Shinnosuke! This way.
Can you put that 'paper'
in my empty left nostril?
Bo! This isn't fun at all!
It isn't fun?
You don't have enough... power.
If you want your desires to come true,
get the power!
Shin chan...
No, Shinnosuke Nohara.
Give me the 'paper'.
Bo?
Fun? Not fun?
Who cares about that.
I want the 'paper'.
I'll get it and become the perfect me!
What can we do?
Shiro?
Masao?
Nasal rinse?
This is pretty nuts.
Masao!
Hey!
- Let's run now!
- Yeah.
I'll power them all up
and catch Shinnosuke Nohara.
Killer Beasts.
Battle mode, maximum level.
You're overreacting.
He's just a kid.
Don't underestimate Shinnosuke Nohara.
He calls up a storm with his farts
and shatters order with his butt.
I'll get the 'paper' at all costs.
Shinnosuke! Who's that girl?
That's Ariana.
Jeez.
What can we do?
Masao, why are you acting like a dog?
You don't know how it feels
to have to become a dog to survive!
The 'paper' in Bo's nose
is going in deeper.
We have to pull it out.
That's not like him.
Bo's is calmer and gentler.
He's a nice boy
who cares about everyone.
A snotless Bo isn't Bo!
Does he have to be snotty all the time?
What is "like him"? Does he have
to be a good boy all the time?
Isn't that just something
that you guys assume?
Do I have to hold back and smile
even if I'm not having fun at all?
I get frustrated, I get angry.
Even when I'm scared and want to cry
I have to smile?
I'm envious.
He can do whatever he wants
and still have everyone cheering him on
and not hating him.
Maybe he's much happier now
that he's not a good boy at all.
No... um... sorry.
Bo is happy?
Snotless Bo is happy?
If Bo is happy, does that mean
we shouldn't pull out that paper?
What do we really know about him?
First we need to run.
The adults are gone!
Did they run away?
Leaving the kid behind?
You're right.
My eyes! My eyes!
There it is! The key!
Good.
We must save Nene and Kazama.
Yeah!
Fugitives detected!
Central garden, West side path A-16.
I repeat. Fugitives detected!
My socks raised in India!
Good!
What?! My socks have no effect!
Maybe cooking curry for so long
made the smell go away
and now they've got a nice, spicy scent?
They smell bad enough.
The scary power of spices.
The children are waiting.
We can't waste time here.
Please, power that lies dormant
inside of me...
...awaken. India power!
My name is Misae Nohara
Daughter of Yoshiji and Hisae Koyama
I was born in Kumamoto
and moved to Tokyo
Married Hiroshi
Became the mother
of Shinnosuke and Himawari
In India, I was entrusted with
Nene, Masao, Toru, and Bo's safety
and became an invincible warrior!
Make way!
Wow wow wow, Make way!
Wow wow wow
Misae Nohara is coming through
India power!
What's up, Shiro?
Master Shiro!
Shiro?
Shiro!
Masao?
Masao!
Shin chan's mom and dad!
I was so scared!
Dad!
Mom!
Shinnosuke!
Nene, Kazama, and Shiro too!
Thank goodness you're all safe.
Jeez, you always get lost
so easily, Mom and Dad.
Aren't you hurt?
What's that word you've been saying?
My new gag.
I dunno what it means,
but Indian people say it all the time.
What? You don't know?
''Dhanyavaad' means 'Thank you'.
Marry thanks for telling me.
Just say "Dhanyavaad."
He managed to get by with just one word?
Our son is really a tough little boy.
Who are you?
Ariana is a friend of mine!
A friend?
You saved Shinnosuke, right?
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Um, it's okay.
Oh no! Let's get out of here!
Damn, they're persistent.
I'll take care of this. You go ahead.
You're making it hard.
Run... get the kids somewhere safe.
Big Bro is right.
Run. Get the kids somewhere safe.
Undercover operation successful.
You're safe!
Of course I am.
I knew you weren't the guy
to meet his end like that.
You got it, Big Bro.
Dill!
Kabir Katchapapal Pakkapapal
Katchapapal Pakkapapal!
Let's sing! India power!
Can you feel it? Inside me
Let's dance! India power!
This way! Let's run while we can.
Pushing forward
On the path of the unknown
We are Hot! Super spicy curry
Looks like a warehouse.
There's a car! Let's go.
Shin chan, what's wrong?
I'm gonna get Bo.
I'm not running away without him.
You're right.
That's why we have to get outta here
now, to save Bo.
You can't give him that piece of paper.
We have to stop Bo
from hurting anyone else.
Yeah.
So, where are we gonna run?
Eep! We're doomed.
They're too many!
There's nowhere to run.
What the...
Come on, let's go!
Get in!
You know how to fly this thing?
I'm going to awaken 120%
of my dormant abilities!
Let's go, India Power!
India power!
I won't let you go.
Dad, go faster!
I'll send a chopper...
I'll go.
Follow my partner!
What?
Oh, no!
The fuel has reached the 'danger zone'!
From the danger zone to the riverbank.
Are you okay, Dear?
What's that?
A bird?
A plane?
Bo!
Fireworks!
This is no time for that!
You get it now?
You can't run away from me.
Give me the 'paper'.
We can't do that.
It's to protect you too, Bo.
Yeah!
Shinnosuke!
Take the 'paper' and run far away.
We'll buy you some time.
Kazama! Nene! Masao!
Kids!
Don't get in my way.
Two pieces of 'paper'
will make me perfect.
Choose, Shinnosuke Nohara.
Give me the 'paper' yourself,
or I'll take it from you.
Don't do it!
Shinnosuke.
I'm gonna get Bo's snot back.
Don't tell me you're going to
stick it up your nose!
Don't do it!
His butt?
Sticking the 'paper' in his butt?
I hadn't thought of that.
By sticking it in his butt
instead of up his nose,
he gets the power, but the evilness
is less likely to come through.
You're the best, Big Bro.
Great insight.
You can do it! Get the 'paper' back,
Lovely Boy Shinnosuke!
Pull out the 'paper'!
No! I want the 'paper'!
No! No! No!
I want the 'paper'!
No!
Pull out the 'paper'!
No! I want the 'paper'!
No!
- Pull out the 'paper'!
- I want the 'paper'!
No! No! No! No!
Nooo!
Bo, are you okay?
Shinnosuke Nohara,
I knew you were no ordinary boy.
But the real showdown starts now.
The 'paper' went completely up his nose!
Lovely Boy Shinnosuke! Run away!
Bo?
This is the perfect me.
India power!
You're too slow. Basically motionless.
A tyrant is born!
It's all over.
No one can stop him now.
Shinnosuke!
Give up!
I'll pull out that 'paper'.
I want to see snotty Bo again.
I told you, no more snot.
You'll give out something,
even if it's not snot.
You'll come up with something fun!
Now you're only letting out
things that aren't fun!
What do you know about me?
So tell me, Bo.
What do you do for fun?
Where do you want to go?
What do you eat? What do you like?
Stop it!
You can't defeat me.
I'm not trying to defeat you.
I just wanna play with you.
Even if you become tyrant Bo,
Pope Bo, or King Bo,
I still wanna play with you!
That's right, Bo.
Let's play.
It's fun!
Even if your nose isn't runny,
even if you change,
I want to have fun with you.
I want to play with you forever!
Let's play, Bo!
Bo!
Bo, let's dance together.
(Futaba Kindergarten Entrance Ceremony)
Bo! Let's dance together.
Because...
We're friends, toot!
A butt-looking stone.
My sideburn of India.
It's "souvenir".
Same difference.
Difference same.
Bo is back!
- Bo! Bo!
- Bo!
Bo is crying.
No, it's snot.
Guys, I'm sorry.
How nice to have friends who like you
even though you've become a tyrant.
I should be smiling
and be happy for them...
But I feel so envious.
I'm such a jerk.
If people knew how selfish I am,
they would all hate me.
Jeez, what am I even saying?
I like you, you know.
It's admirable to be able
to smile and be happy for others.
But sometimes,
we just don't feel like it.
Yeah. Trying to be liked by everyone,
to never do anything wrong
is pretty tough.
Nobody is perfect.
If you were perfect, I couldn't be
with you. It'd be exhausting.
Me too. If you were beautiful,
with a nice personality, a hot body...
plus you were always kind and pleasant,
and could do everything well...
- That wouldn't be bad.
- Hey!
Ariana!
If you stick this up your nostrils,
you'll become almighty.
No! We can't do that.
Let's stick it in.
No one's watching now.
But it was in Bo's nose
and Shin chan's butt. Isn't it dirty?
It's okay!
You won't be a rice ball anymore.
You'll be the strongest
grilled rice ball ever!
You got a point.
What is this?
Naan, isn't it?
Huh? Naan bread?
What's that? Naan?
Rice?
I'm chapati bread.
Big Bro!
The 'paper' is stuck in the chapati!
A tyrant chapati?
Chapati is made of
whole wheat flour and water,
rolled out into a thin, round dough
and baked without yeast.
Remember this.
It's not famous at all in the world.
It's been soundly beaten
by naan and rice.
And now chapati's desire to be famous
has gone out of control!
Just in!
What is this?
This is gonna be terrible!
Run!
It's chapati,
totally unknown in the world!
I found a strongbread.
I'll make you my partner!
Chapati is a wonderful Indian dish.
It pairs deliciously with any curry.
With just a few ingredients
and a little bit of heat,
you can make delicious,
freshly baked chapati.
Chewy and fluffy chapati.
(Chapati)
Superfood Chapati.
Chapati is a wonderful word.
Chapati makes everyone happy.
What is this?
We must pull the paper out
of the chapati!
But it's so up high.
All right! Let's gooo!
No dice.
Why did you think it'd work?
Stay back, kids!
We'll drag it down
and pull the paper out.
In one fell swoop.
India power!
They caught it!
Oh, no!
You bastard! Why?
I'm Urufu the Perfect!
The hottest man in India!
- He needs help!
- Hiroshi!
Oh, no! It's got another arm!
Sorry for the wait.
Principal!
Mhm Uh-huh!
Bunta Takakura!
They've changed way too much.
It's been a tough journey.
We caught the chapati!
What now?
Now! Let's go!
Stop! It's dangerous!
- No!
Together we can go anywhere
They're after the 'paper'?
Yes! This is our world
Even if I'm scared, or cry
Don't worry! Smile
You're not alone
We'll pull out Chapati's 'paper'
and make the world a fun place.
It's over there.
Let's go, Kasukabe Guard! Namaste...
Fire!
It won't come out!
We've got to pull together!
One, two...
Got it!
Let's eat.
Looks tasty.
There's plenty,
so eat as much as you like.
- This one's not spicy.
- Really? Which one?
Yummy!
Ariana,
do you like Shake Shake Bootycure?
Of course!
I like Bootycure Turmeric.
She's cool and cute.
I like Bootycure Ornithine.
What about you, Ariana?
Who do you like?
I'm glad you asked!
The Bootycure I like the most...
Everyone has so many buddies...
But no human, no animal,
not even a chapati wants me.
Why can't I have a partner?
I think you can't find a partner
or a friend by trying too hard.
It's okay to be alone. Don't compare
yourself with others. Be kind.
Be sillier
and enjoy what you like to do.
If you can be your best friend
and make yourself smile,
one day you'll overcome
all kinds of differences,
and a great partner will just show up
by your side.
- Right?
- Uh-huh.
- Tuck in.
- Let's all eat chapati.
I want naan.
Thanks.
What a 'naansense' day!
I'm glad no one was hurt
and we got to eat chapati too.
You're always right, Big Bro.
And finally, the 'paper'
we've been searching for so long...
Where is it?
I'm glad I found the right paper.
There's no paper in Indian toilets
Even if there is, you can't flush it
- You used the 'paper'?
– For your butt?
Do you want it?
Nooo!
No? Okay then.
Big Bro! The 'paper' is burning!
We just have to accept it.
Want some chapati, old man?
Don't call me that, Shinnosuke.
My name is Kabir Katchapapal
Pakkapapal Katchapapal Pakkapapal.
Beer Ketchup Paparazzi
Catch the Ball Pass the Ball?
Kabir Katchapapal Pakkapapal
Katchapapal Pakkapapal!
Say it three times.
I did.
Now say my name, Shinnosuke.
Didn't catch it.
Say it three more times.
Hey!